Guide to the Krishna Reddy Papers MC.244
New York University Archives
Krishna Reddy Papers
1924-2018
1955-2012
New York University Archives
Reddy, Judy Blum
Reddy, Krishna, 1925-2018
MC.244
11.25 Linear Feet in 6 record cartons, 4 flat boxes, 5 manuscript boxes, 1 folder in a shared manuscript box, and 2 folders in a shared oversize box.
The Krishna Reddy Papers were created in conjunction with the life and career of Krishna Reddy, a longtime professor of art at New York University. Most of the collection's materials reflect Reddy's work as a teacher or as a printmaker, and include solo and group exhibition catalogs, as well as programs, promotional materials, and audiovisual footage of workshops. Some materials are of a documentary nature, and include transcribed and taped interviews with Reddy, newspaper articles, and a hardcover book on his career. The collection also contains two hardcover books written by Reddy on printmaking methods.
Conditions Governing Access
Administrative records and unpublished reports of New York University are closed for a period of 20 years from the date of their creation. Access to files spanning multiple years will be opened to researchers based on the date of the most recent materials. Board of Trustees records are closed for 35 years from the date of creation. Materials related to personnel, grievances, job and fellowship searches and applications, and all files that fall under the federal Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA) are permanently restricted. Additional restrictions may apply to other materials in this collection. For questions regarding specific restrictions, please contact the University Archives.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Krishna Reddy Papers were donated to the New York University Archives by Krishna and Judy Blum Reddy in 2014, with an additional donation by Judith Blum Reddy in 2019. The accession numbers associated with these gifts are 14.014 and 2019.039.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged chronologically within each series, with the exception of Series I: Correspondence; this is alphabetically arranged. Files from a 2019 accretion were placed at the end of listings within appropriate series.
The collection is arranged into six series.
Correspondence
Exhibition Materials
Publicity and Biographical Materials
Teaching and Written Works
Photographs
Audiovisual Materials
Biographical Note
Krishna Reddy, a printmaker, professor of art, and author, was born in Chittoor, India, in 1925.
Reddy began his art studies under poet-artist Rabindranath Tagore, receiving a Diploma of Fine Arts from Vishva-Bharati University in 1946. He taught at a Madras art school until 1950 before emigrating to Europe, where he continued training as a painter and sculptor. His first teacher, at London's Slade School of Fine Arts, was semi-abstract sculptor Henry Moore. In 1951, Reddy earned a Certificate of Fine Arts and moved to Paris, where he studied in Ossip Zadkine's studio.
Reddy's reputation as an artist grew throughout the 1950s and 1960s. He began showing his work internationally in the late 1950s, and soon Reddy was receiving regular invitations to participate in group and solo exhibitions. In 1965, he joined his mentor Stanley William Hayter as co-director of Atelier 17. The Paris printmaking workshop was famed for its experimental work; in 1988, Reddy would author "New Ways of Color Printmaking," detailing the innovative techniques he had developed at Atelier 17. In recognition of these new methods, the government of India honored Reddy with the Padma Shri Award in 1972.
Upon leaving Atelier 17 in 1976, Reddy joined the art faculty of New York University's Art and Art Education department. He was appointed as a full-time Professor of Art the following year. During his 25-year tenure at the School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions (now the Steinhardt School of Culture, Education, and Human Development), Reddy directed numerous printmaking workshops and served as Director of the Graphics and Printmaking Program. As a visiting professor, he also instructed student artists at The Cooper Union; University of California, Santa Cruz; University of California, Davis; University of Wisconsin--Madison; and Carnegie Mellon University.
Reddy was named Professor Emeritus at NYU in 2001. Krishna Reddy died in 2018.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Some audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact University Archives with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Scope and Contents
The Krishna Reddy Papers relate to the life and career of Krishna Reddy, a longtime professor of art at New York University. The materials in the collection largely reflect Reddy's work as a teacher or as a printmaker, and include manuscript essay drafts, solo and group exhibition catalogs, as well as programs, promotional materials, and audiovisual footage of workshops and exhibitions. Reddy's personal photographs depict his and his colleagues' artwork of various forms and illustrate his involvement in printmaking workshops and international exhibitions. Some materials are of a biographical nature, and include transcribed and taped interviews with Reddy, newspaper and magazine articles and newsletters.
The Krishna Reddy Papers contain materials from Reddy's time as a student and as a teacher, including copies of works produced by his own mentors and students. As a result, the collection sheds particular insight on the training and development of students of art.
The collection also contains a few published volumes authored by Reddy that detail his printmaking innovations. One hardcover book, Krishna's Cosmos, covers Reddy's career from a biographical perspective.
Sculpture; Newspapers.; Manuscripts for publication.; Art -- Study and teaching.; Prints -- Techniques; Correspondence.; Photographs.; Exhibition catalogs.; Artists' studios; Magazines (periodicals).; Pamphlets.; Books.; Videocassettes.; Dissertations.; Audiocassettes.; DVDs.; Interviews.; Reddy, Judy Blum; Blackburn, Robert Hamilton, 1920-2003; Hayter, Stanley William, 1901-1988; Tagore, Rabindranath, 1861-1941; Masson, Andre, 1896-1987; Zadkine, Ossip, 1890-1967
- Series I: Correspondence, 1945-2008; 246176
  Scope and content
  This series contains correspondence written to Reddy, primarily from art scholars and exhibitors. Personal correspondence is also included.
  - Correspondence A, 1965-2006; 246357 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence B, 1950-2007; 246359 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence C, 1950-2000; 246361 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence D, 1951-2004; 246362 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence E, 1953-1998; 246363 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence F, 1956-2006; 246364 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence G, 1945-2004; 246365 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence H, 1957-2004; 246375 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence I, 1956-2004; 246376 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence J, 1969-2001; 246377 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence K, 1969-2003; 246378 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence L, 1961-2008; 246379 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence M, 1950-2007; 246380 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence N, 1972-2004; 246381 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence O, 1967-2003; 246382 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence P, 1945-2003; 246383 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence Q-R, 1965-2008; 246384 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence S, 1951-2003; 246392 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence T, 1969-1997; 246393 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence U V W, 1957-2005; 246394 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence X Y Z, 1952-1995; 246395 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, 1956-2016 (Box 10, Folder 1-10)
- Series II: Exhibition Materials, 1955-2012; 246177
  This series contains materials relating to the solo and group exhibitions in which Reddy showed his art. Programs, promotional materials, and catalogs, including bound volumes, are included.
  - Exhibitor cards and notices, 1955-1993; 246248 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Exhibition brochures and promotional materials, 1955-1979; 246240 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Exhibition brochures and promotional materials, 1980-2012; 246241 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Exhibition programs and catalogs, 1955-2011; 246242 (Box 2)
  - Poster for "La force vitale" exhibition, 2009 September; 246236 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Exhibition and Course-Related Promotional Material, 1956-2018 (Box 11, Folder 1-11, Box 12, Box 14, Folder 1-6)
  - Exhibition posters, 1977-1990 (Box Shared University Archives 043, Folder 15)
- Series III: Publicity and Biographical Materials, 1951-2012; 246178
  This series includes news clippings, interview transcriptions, and biographical articles and books written about Reddy. Among the books is "Krishna's Cosmos," a 2003 photographic biography of Reddy.
  - Articles and essays on Reddy, undated, 1951-1986; 246404 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - News clippings, 1956-2011; 246418 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - News clippings, 1956-2011; 246862 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - News clippings, 1956-2011; 246863 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Books and periodicals on Reddy, 1959-2011; 246540 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - News clippings--photocopies, 1978-2012; 246407 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Interview tape transcriptions, 1981; 246427 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Interview tape transcriptions, 1981; 246864 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Interviews with students edited by Janet Heit, 1982; 246402 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters and zines, 1986-2006; 246245 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Interview, Curriculum Vitae, Memorial Booklet, Gagan-Abani Puraskar Honor, 1983, circa 1998, 2018, undated (Box 15, Folder 5-7, Box Shared University Archives 088, Folder 5)
- Series IV: Teaching and Written Works, undated, 1968-2004; 246179
  Scope and contents
  This series contains manuscripts and published volumes written by Reddy, as well as programs and promotional materials for his printmaking workshops. Also included are academic works by graduate students Reddy advised at NYU.
  - "Art Expression as a Learning Process" essay, undated; 246244 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Book outline, undated; 246385 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Interview with Andre Masson and other notes, undated; 246415 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - "Materials" preparations--studies and notes, undated; 246398 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Plate preparations--notes for typing, undated; 246387 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Plate preparation--preparation notes, undated; 246386 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - "Processes"--preparations, studies, notes, undated; 246396 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - "State of Mind and the Environment" preparation, undated; 246388 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - "State of Mind and the Environment" preparations--studies and notes, undated; 246400 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Promotional materials--teaching and workshops, undated, 1968-2004; 246243 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - "Materials" preparations--from other books, undated, 1981; 246399 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Writings on art, Vietnam War, teaching, undated, 1987; 246403 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Student thesis proposals, 1984-1985; 246467 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Book outline preparation, circa 1986; 246389 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Kalavahini, circa 1987; 246348 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Intaglio Simultaneous Color Printmaking, 1988; 246858 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Student dissertation--Uttara Asha Coorlawala (4 folders), 1989, 1993-1994; 246469 (Box 4, Folder 3-6)
  - Student dissertation--Gayle Curtis Jones (2 folders), 1992; 246859 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
  - Student thesis proposals, 1992; 246468 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Student dissertation--Sarah Hyde (5 folders), 1993; 246471 (Box 4, Folder 10-14)
  - Student dissertation--Marta Korduba (5 folders), 1994; 246470 (Box 4, Folder 15-19)
  - Student dissertation--Faridah Shaban Mohammad (2 folders), 1994; 246860 (Box 4, Folder 20-21)
  - New Ways of Color Printmaking, 1997; 246861 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - India International Centre Quarterly, 1998; 246346 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Speeches, Lectures, Projects, 1968-1993, undated (Box 14, Folder 7-9)
  - Intaglio Simultaneous Color Printmaking: Significance of Materials and Processes -- Correspondence, Drafts, Reviews, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 10-11, Box 15, Folder 1-4, Box Shared University Archives 043, Folder 14)
- Series V: Photographs, 1924-2009; 246180
  This series contains personal photographs, as well as images depicting Krishna Reddy's artistic career over time. Images in Series V include art prints of Reddy's drawings and photographic prints of his sculptures, as well as images of works by his artistic precursors and mentors, including Joan Miro, Ossip Zadkine, Rabindranath Tagore, and Heinz Leinfellner. Also depicted in the series are scenes from printmaking workshops and Reddy's 1972 receipt of the Padma Shri award. Many images of Reddy's own works contain detailed explanations of artistic technique on their reverse sides.
  - Artwork by others (1 of 3), 1924-1969; 246183 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Artwork by others (2 of 3), undated, 1946-1957; 246184 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Artwork by others (3 of 3), undated, 1945-1960; 246185 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Atelier at Rue Rabelais Sculptures, 1965-1970; 246189 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Carrara--some photos of the place, 1969; 246186 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Drawings, circa 1950s; 246196 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Drawings--prints, undated, 1952, 1971; 246223 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Early prints, 1949-1962; 246191 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Honolulu Art Academy Exhibition, 1987 July; 246187 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Menton, France Photographs, 1951; 246224 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Metal Plates and Prints, 1959-1997; 246221 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Miro and His Work, 1954; 246182 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - NYU Printmaking Shop, circa 1980s; 246190 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - NYU Printmaking Studio, undated; 246231 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Padma Shri at the Ambassador's Home, circa 1972; 246228 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Personal photographs (1 of 2), circa 1980s to 2000s; 246188 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Personal photographs (2 of 2), circa 1950s-1998; 246230 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Prints--Paris, circa 1960s and 1970s; 246200 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Sculptures--12 R. Rabelais, 1959-1965; 246198 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Self-portraits, 1950-1970; 246227 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - St. Margarethan Symposium, Austria, 1961; 246199 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Tobie Steinhouse and Krishna Reddy, 1989 November; 246225 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Trinity College Exhibition--Opening Reception, circa 1980s; 246192 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Workshops and teaching activities, 1970-circa 1990s; 246232 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Workshops, teaching, personal photographs, circa 1960s-1990s; 246195 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Workshops, teaching, sculpture, circa 1960s-1980s; 246229 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Zadkine's Atelier, 1952; 246193 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Zadkine's Atelier--Sculptures (1 of 3), circa 1950s; 246194 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Zadkine's Atelier--Sculptures (2 of 3), circa 1950s; 246226 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Zadkine's Atelier--Sculptures (3 of 3), circa 1950s; 246197 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Series VI: Audiovisual Materials, undated, 1980-1993; 246181
  This series contains audio and audiovisual materials. Audiovisual formats include U-matic, DVD, VHS (some NTSC), and 1/4" audio. Video recordings include interviews with Reddy, as well as footage of his printmaking workshops and artistic process. Four audio tapes also consist of an interview.
  - Krishna Reddy 8 min, undated; 246492; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) 8 minutes; "Heavily used." (Box 4, Item 1)
  - Krishna Reddy 8 min, undated; 246489; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) 8 minutes; "Heavily used tape." (Box 4, Item 2)
  - Krishna rough #2, undated; 246486; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 4, Item 3)
  - KBC Report, New York ch. 53, 1990 May; 246477; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) 8 minutes; Label reads "audio ch I only." (Box 4, Item 4)
  - ECO program channel 2 - Mexico, D.F. interview, undated; 246499; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 8)
  - Interview ECO Program ch 2 - Mexico D.F., undated; 246510; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 8)
  - Krishna Reddy - 39 mins (1 of 2), undated; 246351; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) 39 minutes (Box 8)
  - Krishna Reddy - 39 mins (2 of 2), undated; 246352; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) 39 minutes (Box 8)
  - Krishna Reddy - NYU (Tom Drysdale) + Bronx Museum, undated; 246502; 1 videocassettes (vhs) 39 minutes (Box 8)
  - Krishna with other artists Paris, undated; 246505; 1 videocassettes (vhs); "Krishna Paris. With Ram Kumar / Raza, Akbar NTSC." (Box 8)
  - Krishna with other artists Paris, undated; 246514; 1 videocassettes (vhs); "Krishna - Paris. With Ram Kumar Raza, Akbar. PAL Original 6 Check quality." "Paris-Inde Version 98'" (Box 8)
  - N - R - Eyes - guest Krishna Reddy, undated; 246493; 1 videocassettes (vhs) 24:40 running time; "Montreal sculpture - drawings. Plates. Go to DVD. 25 mins. #1" (Box 8)
  - State of the Art Episode #94 - Krishna Reddy, undated; 246512; 1 videocassettes (vhs); "This goes straight to DVD. Ram 4" (Box 8)
  - Laurent Bregeat film "Krishna Reddy - A Life's Print", undated; 246524; 1 videodiscs (dvd); "A Pundole Art Gallery production In the collection SPECTRUM Testimonies of Indian artists" (Box 8)
  - Pierre Alexis de Potestad film "Krishna", undated; 246525; 1 videodiscs (dvd) (Box 8)
  - Retrospective Exhibition - 3 Master Printmakers, undated; 246526; 1 videodiscs (dvd); "Lee Chesney Krishna Reddy Ken Kerslake" (Box 8)
  - Tape 1, undated; 246528; 1 sound tape reels; "Q's--general -L's intro to art. -K's inspiration to leave India -war influenced K in Paris -move from sculpture to prints -discover v experimentation -political function of arts" (Box 8)
  - Tape 2, undated; 246529; 1 sound tape reels; "-political function of artist (cont.) -How does an artist fight for freedom (-the galleries went to them not vice versa -art is part of living) -Krishna as teacher (he learns more from the student) -clown theme as political -sculpture - Paris 68 (cont.)" (Box 8)
  - Tape 3, undated; 246530; 1 sound tape reels; "May 68 (cont.) sculpture + different materials - not very good development of standing figure theme" (Box 8)
  - Tape 4, undated; 246531; 1 sound tape reels; "materials drawings - + clown Color Print [unint] clown face [unint] shape arena - circus space circle + cross last part about NYU color printing workshop" (Box 8)
  - Krishna Reddy #1 NYU Team 1980, 246513; 1 videocassettes (vhs); "Studio with Tom + Alex Carving metal "Clown Formation" -carving -with Apu - Drawing Prep on metal -colors--rolling on glass plate--small rollers -Printing the plate -Talk on color viscosity -again [unint] explaining -again -again" (Box 8)
  - Krishna Reddy #2 NYU Team 1980, 246507; 1 videocassettes (vhs); "Tom & me -in the classroom with students at NYU -in my studio - plate making with tools (blown copperplate) -Explain plates with prints - '50s --> now - important" (Box 8)
  - Krishna Reddy doc. - 39 min Bronx Museum 1980, 246511; 1 videocassettes (vhs) 39 minutes; "Go to DVD. #2" "Tom Drysdale + me in the studio -Drawing on the plate - Apu [unint] eye -sculptures of titles [unint] -Viscosity [unint] - Jessy Riley -engraving & carving the plate with tools -preparing copper plate "clown & flying swans" and printing in color -NYU class - with students (Box 8)
  - Krishna Paris, 1985; 246495; 1 videocassettes (vhs); "Paris-Inde" "Krishna Reddy / Paris 1985" (Box 8)
  - Paris-Inde 1985 - Krishna Reddy Paris 1985, 246506; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 8)
  - 1 - Class NYU color atelier - master 1, 1990 February 28-March 12; 246503; 1 videocassettes (vhs); "1 Class 2/28/90 NYU color atalier / 3/10/90 (start)" "simultaneous viscosity prints" "Kenkeleba Gallery / Krishna Reddy / Clown - Juggler, 1989" (Box 8)
  - 2 - Krishna master, 1990 March 17-21; 246496; 1 videocassettes (vhs); "2 Kenkeleba interior and exterior (end) 3/17/90 / Class at N.Y.U. 3/21/90 (lecture printing) (most)" (Box 8)
  - 3 - Krishna 3/21/90 master, 1990 March 21-28; 246509; 1 videocassettes (vhs); "3 Class 3/21/90 (to end) / Krishna Reddy at Home 3/28/90 Demon. Power Tools + [unint] of Prints + History" (Box 8)
  - 4 - class printing 4/4/90 4/11/90, 1990 April 4-11; 246515; 1 videocassettes (vhs); "4 Class 4/4/90 / printing mix colors / Discussion of [unint] + viscosity / Class 4/11/90 Pointilism (start)" (Box 8)
  - 5 - 4/18/90 Krishna master, 1990 April 18; 246494; 1 videocassettes (vhs); "5 Class pointilism lecture 4/11/90 (cont'd)" "Class pointilist 4/18/90 (start)" (Box 8)
  - 6 - Krishna 4/25/90 master, 1990 April 18-May 2; 246497; 1 videocassettes (vhs); "6 Class 4/18/90 (cont'd) / Class 4/25/90 Print plate twice (intaglio separate) / Print without viscosity / Last class 5/2/90 (start)" (Box 8)
  - 7 - 5/9/90 Krishna master, 1990 May 2-9; 246500; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 8)
  - Artist Krishna Reddy interview with Masud Alam - New York City 1993, 246498; 1 videocassettes (vhs); "Krishna in studio / good tape 3" (Box 8)
  - Krishna - Rough Cut #1, undated; 246350; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 9)
  - 3/26 #1 Table-tool/Krishna-Apu, undated; 246476; 1 videocassettes (vhs) 20 minutes; Label reads "Krishna working on zink [sic] plate --- clown." (Box 9)
  - Krishna Reddy tape 1 - tape 1 original, undated; 246481; 1 videocassettes (u-matic); Label reads "mix color." (Box 9)
  - Narration tape #1 - K. Reddy story, undated; 246483; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 9)
  - Krishna tape - 2 original, undated; 246479; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 9)
  - 3/26 - Tape 2 Krishna Reddy master, undated; 246480; 1 videocassettes (u-matic); Label reads "drawing with Apu - [unint] on plate." (Box 9)
  - Krishna Reddy - narration tape #2, undated; 246482; 1 videocassettes (u-matic); Labels read "naraton [sic] no picture," "Eric Early, Krish. Narration #2," "E. Early / P. Smith." (Box 9)
  - Krishna tape 3 original, undated; 246485; 1 videocassettes (u-matic); Label reads "Krishna colour mixing - roller [unint]." (Box 9)
  - Tape 3 - March 28 Krishna Reddy master, 1981 March 28; 246484; 1 videocassettes (u-matic); Unintelligible label. (Box 9)
  - Krishna Reddy - tape 4 original, undated; 246474; 1 videocassettes (vhs) (Box 9)
  - Tape 4 - 3/27/81 Krishna Reddy master, 1981 March 27; 246487; 1 videocassettes (u-matic); "Shots of prints" (Box 9)
  - Krishna Reddy tape 5 original, 1981 March 28; 246491; 1 videocassettes (u-matic) (Box 9)
  - Krishna Reddy - tape 5 master, 1981 March 28; 246478; 1 videocassettes (vhs); Label reads "edit trouble." (Box 9)
  - Krishna Reddy - tape 6 original, undated; 246473; 1 videocassettes (vhs); Label reads "working with zinc plate." (Box 9)
  - Krishna Reddy - tape 6 master, undated; 246475; 1 videocassettes (vhs) 20 minutes; Label reads "Tape #6 Master Krishna Reddy/Class (Mon 3/30) -- working with plate." (Box 9)
  - Krishna Reddy tape #7 original, undated; 246490; 1 videocassettes (u-matic); "Macro of 'Rhyme Broken' print on tail." (Box 9)
  - Krishna Reddy - original tape 8, undated; 246488; 1 videocassettes (u-matic); Label unintelligible. (Box 9)